

CONTACTS



+37068127238



arnoldasstrukcinskas@gmail.com



Kaunas



LinkedIn profile



My Projects



My Web Page

TECH STACK

- Back-End: Java, Spring Boot, C++,
- Front-End: HTML, CSS, JS
- Database: MySQL, PostgreSQL
- Tools: Git, IntelliJ, CLion, Visual
- Additional: Azure cloud(basics), FTP(basics), Axure, AutoCad

JOB EXPERIENCE

Pool technical specialist/lifeguard UAB "Eglės" sanatorium 2021-07 - 2024-06

Car fleet maintanance/manager Citybee, UAB "PrimeLeasing" 2021-04 - 2021-12

Physiotherapy UAB "Eglės" sanatorium 2018-07 - 2021-07

LANGUAGES

- Lithuanian (Native)
- Russian (Near-native)
- English (B2 lygis)

ARNOLDAS STRUKČINSKAS

Junior Back-End developer

ABOUT ME

Programming has been my passion since adolescence. I am currently studying Software Systems at Vilnius College and actively deepening my knowledge. I have a strong work ethic, can work well in a team, and solve technical challenges independently.

EDUCATION

Software developer bachelor's degree

2024 - now Wilnius college

Sports physiotherapy master's degree

2019 - 2021

Lithuanian University of Health sciences

Physiotherapy bachelor's degree

2015 - 2019

Lithuanian University of Health sciences

PROJECTS

2D platformer game | Link

- Created with C++
- Graphical design made with SFML library
- 2D RPG type game

BattleShips game | Link

- · Created using Java and Spring Boot
- Usual BattleShips game

COURSES

JAVA software development

Vilnius Coding School

Java Programming Masterclass updated to Java 17

Udemy.com

135.5h

C# Basics for Beginners: Learn C# Fundamentals by Coding

Udemy.com

5.5h